{
    "id": "059fc45ebe184faba938e94ebfd0417f",
    "title": "Prepositions Worksheet",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "What are you thinking .......................?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "at",
                "with",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7056929391a34038804113813db6c314"
        },
        {
            "question": "You are the person I was looking ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "75072f2b17a8469e85f6876a799ae7c8"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is not very easy to work …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "about",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "725cfeff0dad452e94e4ebe71ad3e63f"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is not very easy to talk …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "at",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ca4fe0e4bbbe4789a814cc2bd961a7f5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am not certain ………………. what I am supposed to do.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "to",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1aacf56fbcbc4ffebf2b82d535e0f5b3"
        },
        {
            "question": "She enjoys being looked ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "381c36faad7f424d9a8623657d64c53f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I hate being shouted …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "at",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ce55b7bf61644b30933232b33e0140ab"
        },
        {
            "question": "She saved money ………………. giving up smoking.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8653c0fbd9e748b3b71944db7ac20f9b"
        },
        {
            "question": "She rang me ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6b1115ce72bc40e3abf89611a0f0014d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I half believe ……………….. life after death.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a164f9d9bde64c22b88af26ee45657f9"
        },
        {
            "question": "My parents never showed if they were disappointed ……………….. me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7bb2c1a592a7453d86051a45e07f8599"
        },
        {
            "question": "I would like to see a big increase ………………. productivity.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4eae10aa62584bb3942a856e8a40e1b4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am very impressed …………….. your work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "by",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6a1263a66a024cdbab9b93ea4471dc8c"
        }
    ]
}